SANGRAM SUNDARAY

DATA SCIENTIST & SOFTWARE DEVELOPER
[DEEP LEARNING / DJANGO / VUE]

Phone: 993-782-6218

E-mail: emails.sangram@gmail.com

Website: sangramz.github.io

PROFILE

5+ years of experiences in Deep Learning (Using both Pytorch & Pyspark), Cloud Services in Azure & AWS, Django & LAMP stack Development, VueJs,

Had also worked in Digital Marketing, Google Search console & Analytics and ML using Tensorflow

EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Neukelp Innovation (Jan 2019 - Mar 2019)

- Project in collaboration with PwC Developed prototype for Document Abstraction
- Developed Named Entity Recognition Model and Legal Text Analysis.
- App Development : Using VueJs & Django Rest API
- Maintained Code Repository

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

SITSIndia (Jan 2014 - October 2018)

- Applied decision tree analysis, Statistical Analysis & Predictive Modelling
- Web Apps Development in LAMP Stack, Python-Django Stack & WordPress
- Managing Development team to Meet Projects Deadlines

MANAGEMENT TRAINEE (SALES)

AuroIN LLP (Aug 2013 - Dec 2013)

- Sales Prospecting & Operations (US & UK Region)
- Business Communication (Skype & Phone Call)

SKILLS

- Deep learning & ML: Using Pytorch & Tensorflow, PySpark (Personal Preference, Pytorch & PySpark), Scikit-Learn, NLP Basics (Using NLTK - For Named Entity Recognition)
- Data Analysis: Numbpy, Panda
- Front-End: VueJs, Bootstrap CSS & JS
- **Backend**: Django, mySQL, Django REST API framework.
- Cloud Services: Azure, AWS S3 & Lambdas, Docker
- TDD, Unit Testing & Agile Development, Version control(Using Git)

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING

Biju Patnaik University of Technology - 2013

• Electronics & Communication

XTH XII SCIENCE

K. V. HPCL Jagiroad, Assam - 2008

OTHER DETAILS

+91 - 993-782-218

emails@sangram@gmail.com

760, Lane 1, JV Bhubaneswar - 751013